Guide to the Rabinowitz, Boudin, Standard, Krinsky and Lieberman Legal Files TAM.287
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Legal Work and Client Files, 1915-1992
  - ACA: Western Union - Western Union v. Selly, Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - ACA: Western Union - Western Union v. Selly, Notes, Drafts, Fragments, 1946, Undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - ACA: Western Union - Western Union v. Selly, Stenographer's Minutes, Jan 31, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - ACA: Western Union - Western Union v. Selly, Stenographer's Minutes, Feb 1, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - ACA: Western Union - Western Union v. Selly, Transcripts and Memoranda, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - ACA: Western Union - Western Union v. Western Union International(Complaint re 1971 Strike), 1971-1972 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - ACA: Wholesale Laundry Board of Trade v. City of New York, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - ACA: Xerox Merger, 1979-1983 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York City Opera Orchestra - Contract, 1973-1974 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Actuarial Reports, 1964-1973 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Agreements, 1970-1976 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Basic Pension Plan, Contract, 1965-1969 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Collective Bargaining, Agreements, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Collective Bargaining, Agreements, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Collective Bargaining, Agreements, 1968-1971 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Collective Bargaining, Agreements, 1973-1976 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Collective Bargaining, Contracts (Other Orchestras), 1963, Undated (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Collective Bargaining, Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Collective Bargaining, Correspondence (I), 1970-1974 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Collective Bargaining, Correspondence (II), 1970-1974 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Collective Bargaining, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Documents, 1970-1974 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Drafts, [1967]-[1973], Undated (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Financial Statements, 1969-1973 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Insurance Certificates, Undated (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Meetings, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Meetings, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Meetings, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Meetings, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Meetings, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Meetings, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Meetings, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Memoranda, 1967-1976 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Notes, 1967, Undated (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Proposals, Agreements and Negotiations, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Proposals, Agreements and Negotiations, 1967-1970 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Proposals, Agreements and Negotiations, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Proposals, Agreements and Negotiations, 1973-1976 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Spanish Tour, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: New York Philharmonic - Tax Returns, 1962-1963, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: Radio City Music Hall, 1955-1957 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Bandes v. Harlow and Jones, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Bank Markazi, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Black Panther Bail and Defense Funds: Agreement, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Black Panther Bail and Defense Funds: Financial Records, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Black Panther Bail and Defense Funds: General Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Bill of Rights Foundation, 1965-1967 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Bonnano, Joseph Charles, Jr. v. USA: Petition for Writ of Certiorari, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Boudin, Leonard: Fundraiser for Socialist Workers Party Suit, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Boudin, Leonard: "The Orangeburg Massacre" - Drafts and Research, 1968-1970, 1979-1980 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Burchett v. Kane, 1969-1975 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Case Research: Education, 1971-1972, Undated (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Civil Liberties Civil Defense Fund, 1961-1973 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Civil Service Technical Guild (CSTG), Local 375: Accountants' Reports, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Albano, Louis G. et al. v. Richard Izzo, et al.(I), 1981-1983 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Albano v. Izzo(II), 1981-1983 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Albano, Louis G., W. Bradley Smith, George Wendt, et al. v. Richard Izzo, et al.- Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Albano, Smith, Wendt, et al. v. Izzo- Court Documents (I), 1982 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Albano, Smith, Wendt, et al. v. Izzo- Court Documents (II), 1982 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Albano, Smith, Wendt, et al. v. Izzo- Court Documents, 1982-1983 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Albano, Smith, Wendt, et al. v. Izzo- Deposition of Izzo, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Albano, Smith, Wendt, et al. v. Izzo- Exhibits, 1979-1980 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Albano, Smith, Wendt, et al. v. Izzo- Exhibits, 1978-1980 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Albano, Smith, Wendt, et al. v. Izzo- Notes, [1982]-[1984], Undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Budgets, 1981, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Civil Service Pay Plan, 1979-1986 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - CSTG, Local 375: CSTG v. Edward Koch, Mayor(I), 1979-1982 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - CSTG, Local 375: CSTG v. Edward Koch, Mayor(II), 1979-1982 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - CSTG, Local 375: CSTG v. Edward Koch, Mayor(III), 1979-1982 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - CSTG, Local 375: CSTG v. Edward Koch, Mayor(IV), 1979-1982 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - CSTG, Local 375: CSTG v. Edward Koch, Mayor- Related Cases, 1980-1981 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Consentino, et al. v. Evans and Pennachio, 1981-1982 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Consolidation of Several Job Series, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Contract and John Muller Medical Coverage Issue, 1980-1984 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Documents - Certifications, 1975-1984 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Documents - Constitutions, 1976-1985 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Documents - Contracts (I), 1978-1981 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Documents - Contracts (II), 1978-1981 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Dougall v. Sugarman, Bopardikar, P.V., 1983-1984 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Elections, 1982, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Executive Order 75, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Feeney, Thomas R. and Bryce, Mark v. Louis G. Albano et al., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - CSTG, Local 375: File Index, 1992, Undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Finances, Bills, 1983-1986 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Finances, Hours, 1984-1986 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Finances, Retainer Agreements, 1981-1990 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Firm's Activities, Memos, 1981-1989, Undated (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - 1989 Ethics in Government Act (I), 1987-1989 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - 1989 Ethics in Government Act (II), 1987-1989 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Agreement with Griffin Media Group, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Air Cleaner, 1989-1990 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Background Investigation, Negotiations with Board of Education (I), 1984-1986 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Background Investigation, Negotiations with Board of Education (II), 1984-1986 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Challenge to 1985 Chapter 7 Officer Elections, 1985-1986 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Court Review of Salary Review Board, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Criminal Defense Fund and Benefits, 1987, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Dependent Care Assistance Plan, 1984-1987 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Diaz, Eduardo, 1989-1990 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Discrimination Complaint, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Election Challenge 1984, 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Employee/Debtor Questionnaire, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Financial Disclosure, Confidentiality Provision, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Financial Disclosure, Memos re Forms, 1984-1990 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Financial Disclosure, Memo re Waiver, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Financial Disclosure, Research, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Financial Disclosure, Waiver Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Financial Disclosure, Waiver of Right to Sue (Research), Undated (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - FOIA Request, School Construction Authority, 1989-1990 (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Information re Richard Izzo, 1978-1980 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Information re Richard Izzo, Bank Statements and Cancelled Checks, 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Information re Richard Izzo, Questions, 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Interagency Transfer Rights, 1982, 1987-1989 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Lease Problems, 1981, 1983, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Liability of Employees, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - MTA Coalition, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Non-Competitive and Exempt Titles, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB) Amendments, 1988-1989 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Overtime Payment, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Professional Employees Legal Services (PELS), Conflict of Interest, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - PELS, Family House Closings, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - PELS, Liability Insurance, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Retirees' Rights, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Reward / Marchetti Homicide, 1989-1990 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Second Challenge to Broadbanded Chemist Titles, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Transit Benefits, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Use of Consultants, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - Waiver of Title VII Rights, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - CSTG, Local 375: General Assistance - WNYC Inquiry re Civil Service, 1989-1990 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Grievances, 1976-1981 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Guido, Dan v. Local 375, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Health and Hospital Corporation -- Decentralization, 1979-1981 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Health and Hospital Corporation - General Problems, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Health and Security Fund Embezzlement, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Inspector General (IG) Hearings and Materials, 1967-1981 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Izzo, Richard v. Louis G. Albano- Correspondence, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Izzo v. Albano- Court Documents, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Izzo v. Albano- Court Documents, Briefs, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Izzo v. Albano- Deposition of Izzo, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Izzo v. Albano- Research, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Izzo v. Albano- Supreme Court (NY), 1981-1984 (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Izzo v. Albano- Supreme Court (NY), Court Documents (I), 1984 (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Izzo v. Albano- Supreme Court (NY), Court Documents (II), 1984 (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Izzo, Richard et al. v. CSTG, Local 375(I), 1982 (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Izzo, Richard et al. v. CSTG, Local 375(II), 1982 (Box 87, Folder 33)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Izzo, Richard et al. v. CSTG, Local 375(III), 1982 (Box 87, Folder 34)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Levy, Mel - Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Malpractice Insurance, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Meeting Minutes - Board of Delegates, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Meeting Minutes - Delegate Body, 1983-1985 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Meeting Minutes - Executive Board / Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Meeting Minutes - General Membership, 1980-1986 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Metz, Harry - Charges re Dues Increase, 1980-1982 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - City Island Marina Study / Moberg Termination, 1980-1982 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - City Island Chamber of Commerce, 1972-1981 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Disciplinary Manual, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Exhibits, City, 1967-1981 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Exhibits, Union, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Exhibits, Joint, 1981-1982 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Formal File, 1981-1982 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Grievance Materials, 1981-1982, Undated (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Grievance Materials, Various, 1975-1982 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Individuals Involved, 1980-1981 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Labor Arbitration Reports, Undated (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB) Decisions, 1974, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Petition, [1982] (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Publicity, Press, 1981-1982 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Subpoenas, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Research re First Amendment, 1967, 1978, Undated (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Moberg, Peggy - Working Papers and Notes, 1981, Undated (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Notes, 1984, Undated (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Pensions, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Professional Employee Legal Services (PELS) - Address List, Trustees, 1978, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Advisory Committee, 1981-1986 (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Attorneys' Reports and Memos to Trustees, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Benefits Fund Trust Agreement, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Expense Account of Previous Trustees, 1980-1981 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Financial Report, 1979-1982 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Funding Agreements, 1983-1984 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Information re Municipal Employees Legal Services (MELS), 1977-1978, Undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Insurance, 1978-1982 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Insurance Scam, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Liability Insurance, 1986-1987 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Memos, 1981-1982 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - "Misc.", 1980-1981, Undated (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - New Jersey Office, 1983-1984 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Notes, 1981, Undated (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Questionnaire to Membership, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - CSTG, Local 375: PELS - Reimbursement for Attending Trustees Meeting, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Professional Scientists and Technicians of America, 1979-1981 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Rebates, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Review for Possible Action, 1979-1981 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Sherman, Fred, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Sublease w/DC 37 Benefit Trust Fund, 1981, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Supervisor of School Maintenance Titles - Broadbanding, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Thomas National, Inc., 1981 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transfers, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority, Administrative Titles - Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority, Administrative Titles - Correspondence re OCB Decision, 1974-1985 (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority, Administrative Titles - DC 37 Challenge re Superintendents, [1984] (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority, Administrative Titles - Memos, 1978, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority, Administrative Titles - Notes, 1983, 1985, Undated (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority, Administrative Titles - Organizational Charts, 1984-1985, Undated (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority, Administrative Titles - Organizational Charts, Undated (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority, Administrative Titles - Settlement, 1984-1987 (Box 89, Folder 33)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority, Administrative Titles - Tables of Organization (I), 1985-1986 (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority, Administrative Titles - Tables of Organization (II), 1985-1986 (Box 89, Folder 35)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority - Transit Material #1, 1981-1986 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority - Transit Material #1, 1984-1986 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority - Transit Material #1, 1984-1987 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority - Transit Material #2, 1981-1985, Undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority - Transit Material #2, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority - Transit Material #2, 1985-1986 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority - Transit Material #3, 1984-1987 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority - Transit Material #3, Undated (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority - Transit Material #4, 1856, 1968, 1984-1985 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Authority - Transit Material #4, 1985, Undated (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Transit Derailment Hearing, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Trust Funds - General, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Trust Funds - Benefit Trust Fund (I), 1977-1983 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Trust Funds - Benefit Trust Fund (II), 1977-1983 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Trust Funds - Education Trust Fund (I), 1977-1981 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Trust Funds - Education Trust Fund (II), 1977-1981 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - CSTG, Local 375: Trust Funds - Trust Fund Agreement, 1981-1983 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - C ole v. Loew's: Letter, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Conal, Bernard: Hearing Testimony, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Black Caucus, National Urban League and Various Other African-American Organizations, 1972-1974 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Conscientious Objector Status: Gordon, James M.D., 1969-1971 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Conscientious Objector Status: Tuchin, Terry M.D., 1970-1971 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Conscientious Objector Status: Weinstein, Jay Allen, 1965-1966 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Cuba: Telex re Harry Belafonte and Nat King Cole, Undated (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Dash, Stephen: Army Security Board Hearing (Anti-War Activity / Socialist Party Membership), 1969 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Dash, Stephen: Army Security Board Hearing (Anti-War Activity / Socialist Party Membership) - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Dash, Stephen: Army Security Board Hearing (Anti-War Activity / Socialist Party Membership) - DA 201 File, 1967-1969 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Dash, Stephen: Army Security Board Hearing (Anti-War Activity / Socialist Party Membership) - Notes, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Dash, Stephen: Army Security Board Hearing (Anti-War Activity / Socialist Party Membership) - Transcript (I), 1969 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Dash, Stephen: Army Security Board Hearing (Anti-War Activity / Socialist Party Membership) - Transcript (II), 1969 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Deane, Hugh: Navy, Loyalty Issue, Communist Party, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - District 65: USA v. Livingston, David and Paley, Jack, 1951-1952 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Draft Petition for Certiorari re 1979 to Protest Visit of Teng Xiao-Ping (Box 91, Folder 17)